okay yeah recording okay so um good
好的，录音很好，很好
evening around I've created the few jobs
晚上，我创造了一些工作
in the Jenkins on Eclipse and basically
在Eclipse上的Jenkins中，基本上
I should start with TCK TCK is used for
我应该从TCK开始TCK用于
making sure that the implementation was
确保实施是
always comfortable with the API with the
始终对API感到满意
standard and for it for the Jakarta ee8
标准，并适用于Jakarta ee8
release we probably do a bit different
发布，我们可能会有所不同
thing we wanted to be sure that the new
我们要确保新事物
API which is going to be released in
即将发布的API
Egypt ie a to be comfortable the Java EE
埃及即一个舒适的Java EE
8 and for that we wanted to use the TCK
8，为此，我们想使用TCK
so basically the idea is that if we have
所以基本上的想法是，如果我们有
the GlassFish the implementation which
GlassFish的实现
was already compatible which passed all
已经兼容，通过了所有
the TCK tests then we just have the
TCK测试，那么我们只有
implementation which is compatible so if
兼容的实现，如果
we put in the new API and we read under
我们放入新的API，然后阅读
D CK then it all should become if it
D CK，那一切应该变成
passed and it all should be comfortable
通过了，一切都应该舒服
as well that's what the other thing to
这就是另一件事
do we just have few jobs and basically
我们只有很少的工作吗？
there is the job needed for the API to
API需要完成以下工作
be built so that's probably the job for
被建造，所以这可能是工作
ya I'll show you that on the Jason B on
我会在Jason B上向您展示
Jason B we use
我们使用的Jason B
the build job from which builds the API
从中构建API的构建作业
from the efore j8 branch and we then we
从efore j8分支开始，然后我们
put that to do API to GlassFish so and
把它做为GlassFish的API这样
we built the TCK bundle we build we run
我们构建了我们运行的TCK捆绑包
the TCG bundling and that's it so the
TCG捆绑销售就是这样
build job has the artifact which which
建立工作有哪些工件
is going to be used in our TCK job and I
将用于我们的TCK工作，我
can show you here this this GlassFish
可以在这里给你看这个GlassFish
integration job just takes that API and
集成工作只是采用该API，
integrates it into GlassFish it has
将其集成到它具有的GlassFish中
another artifact which is the GlassFish
另一个工件是GlassFish
containing the new API built from the e4
包含从e4构建的新API
j by a branch and there is the TC k r
j由一个分支并且存在TC kr
envelope which just takes this GlassFish
只需要这个GlassFish的信封
and runs to build TC k against the
并运行以建立TC k
GlassFish so what what is most important
GlassFish那么最重要的是什么
in these settings is the TSgt
在这些设置中是TSgt
configuration file the TSgt
配置文件TSgt
collaboration files just basically the
协作文件基本上
main file which is needed to be
需要的主文件
configured to do around the TCK TCK asan
配置为围绕TCK做TCK asan
based projects it's a basically TSgt
基于项目，基本上是TSgt
file contains mainly the class
文件主要包含类
but which is given yond and the class
但是那是超越了阶级的
but this is only used for the TCK to be
但这仅用于TCK
done so I'm TSgt file TSgt file is
完成，所以我是TSgt文件TSgt文件是
located for every project in the
位于
original Jakarta eg CK repository it's
原始的雅加达，例如CK仓库
in your install folder and under each
在您的安装文件夹中，并在每个
project for instance Jason B there is
例如Jason B的项目
beneful der where the TSgt file is
TSgt文件所在的位置
located
位于
this ESET file is not filled in as just
此ESET文件不完全按照
plain file and you can see there is
普通文件，您可以看到有
basically mostly in most projects there
基本上在大多数项目中
is some Jason B classes or Jason B or
是一些Jason B班还是Jason B或
import classes or a similar property
导入类或类似属性
which is needed to be filled with with
需要用
the correct class path so um there is
正确的课堂路径
few other properties which are already
其他一些已经存在的属性
set and there are maybe some more which
设置，也许还有更多
are not Jason B is quite simple D CK say
不是贾森B是很简单的D CK说
there is not many much properties but
物业不多，但
the the Jenkins jobs for us fills the
詹金斯的工作为我们填补了
file with the needed properties I can I
我可以使用具有所需属性的文件
can if I if I walk to the configuration
如果我走到配置可以
settings of the file like so basically
文件的设置基本上像这样
what what's there there is
那里有什么
the classpath and all the charts are
类路径和所有图表
needed for the TCK to be round and which
TCK需要圆角的，并且
I needed to be put to class spot and
我需要上课地点
this is a bit unclear what jaws from
这有点不清楚
classification needs to be on the class
分类需要上课
path basically the original
路径基本上是原始的
documentation covered that the I don't
文档涵盖了我不
think there is a documentation we show
认为有我们显示的文档
the colors just now right right now
现在的颜色
maybe maybe this I'm not quite sure see
也许也许我不太确定
basically what can be done if the TCK is
基本上，如果TCK是
being built to the Java compiler that
被构建到Java编译器
doesn't find some class or say so that's
没有找到任何课程或说这样的话
that's the class which is needed to be
这是需要的课程
put into class path so that's that's
进入课堂路径，那就是
probably what properties are here we
大概这里有什么属性
have employee I which is always the
有员工我总是
guards fish something together have
守卫一起钓鱼的东西
settings for Tomcat as well but
Tomcat的设置
GlassFish is default I use a property
我默认使用GlassFish属性
web home which probably is not in the
网路首页，可能不在
TSgt file anywhere so I needed to append
TSgt文件在任何地方，所以我需要附加
this property it's basically a shortcut
这个属性基本上是一个快捷方式
to the GlassFish home oh yeah here it's
到GlassFish的家哦，是的，这是
uh it's it's a seven home property
呃，这是七套房
it's the clasp is the physical location
扣子是物理位置
on that Jenkins machine where the
在那个詹金斯机器上
GlassFish will be deployed for the t ck
GlassFish将部署到此
to be run sir and many TC case use web
先生要运行，许多TC案例都使用网络
server home which is always low Costa
服务器主页总是很低的Costa
and web support
和网络支持
depends on what is the default the
取决于默认值是多少
default for GlassFish is 80 80 so
GlassFish的默认值为80 80，所以
basically that's all it can what needs
基本上就可以满足需求
to be set for four days Jason B case so
被定为四天的杰森B案，所以
the job just grabs the DSG defiled the
这项工作只是抓住了DSG file污的
original one then it fills that and
原始的然后填充
what's next
下一步是什么
it just archives the DSG D file the dat
它只是将DSG D文件存档
files used for both t ck build and TC
用于tck构建和TC的文件
Karen so when when the TSgt file is
凯伦所以当TSgt文件是
created then the t ck can be built the t
创建然后可以构建t ck
ck if i go to the configuration settings
ck，如果我进入配置设置
the D CK is build well for a TCK to be
D CK可以很好地构建TCK
built the implementation or the API is
建立实施或API是
all DPS I needed and the the api's are
我需要的所有DPS和api是
all located in the glassfish and the
全部位于玻璃鱼和
GlassFish is just grabbed from the maven
GlassFish只是从专家那里抢来的
central and for the build for the d ck
中央和为d ck构建
built we can use just this unmodified
内置的，我们可以使用未经修改的
GlassFish
玻璃鱼
so hmm the dck repository is cloned into
因此，将dck存储库克隆到
into the CTS folder I I just choose CES
进入CTS文件夹II，只需选择CES
follow with this a whole Jakarta EDC
跟随整个雅加达EDC
case is cloned in that folder and ie da
case克隆在该文件夹中，即da
I cloned or grabbed the media's jte file
我克隆或抓取了媒体的jte文件
which we filled previously to the
我们之前填充到
download folder and here's a small
下载文件夹，这是一个小
script basically the largest part of the
脚本基本上是
script is to grab the T the tcks
剧本是抢T头
arm-based project and it expects the t
基于手臂的项目，它期望
ck to be on exact location in GC k the
ck位于GC k的确切位置
TC k repository does not contain yond so
TC k存储库不包含
this scrape just grabs on from from some
这种刮擦只是从一些
web location and it deploys it in the
网站位置并将其部署在
location which is expected so it's the d
预期的位置，所以它是
ck home and tools subfolder so yeah
ck家和工具子文件夹等等
there it is expected of course I said on
在那里，我当然会说
home to that very location so the ant is
那个位置的家，所以蚂蚁是
executed from there I unzip the
从那里执行我解压缩
GlassFish and most of the TC Kasich need
GlassFish和大多数TC Kasich需求
a need just 3 environment variables to
只需3个环境变量即可
be set before the TC case can be can be
可以在TC案例可以被设置之前设置
built and executed it stays home it's
建立并执行它留在家里
diaz home is basically the property
豪宅基本上是物业
which says
这说
where did TCK is located Syria in this
TCK在哪里位于叙利亚
belt scrape it's basically we're from
皮带刮擦基本上是我们来自
the TCK is going to be built then there
TCK将要建造，然后在那里
is the deliverable there this property
该属性是否可交付使用
needs to be named like this there is
需要像这样命名
sort of an scripts in in the TCK which
TCK中的一种脚本
expects this property to be set so um
希望将此属性设置为um
not only is it corresponds to the folder
它不仅对应于文件夹
in the TCK workspace it also is referred
在TCK工作空间中，它也被引用
to by an scripts during the build step
在构建步骤中由脚本执行
so and
所以和
there is a Java EE home property which
有一个Java EE主页属性
is which points to where I unzipped the
指向我解压缩的位置
GlassFish see the client TCK repository
GlassFish查看客户端TCK存储库
is deployed somewhere
部署在某个地方
the TSgt file is replaced and and built
TSgt文件被替换并构建
all is cold and it said it creates it
一切都很冷，它说它创造了它
creates some a dck bundle in the release
在发行版中创建一些dck捆绑包
folder and it's just it's just saved as
文件夹，只是将其另存为
an artifact in bas build actions so if I
bas构建动作中的伪像，如果我
show you here there is the TCK TCK
告诉你这里有TCK TCK
bundle and there is some documentation
捆绑，有一些文档
which contains some information some
其中包含一些信息
node and there is also exclude list I
节点，并且还有排除列表I
don't think there is any exclude
不要以为有任何排除
excluded test right now in the TC k but
现在在TC k中排除了测试，但
maybe at this so this exclude list can
也许在这个，所以这个排除列表可以
be used when the D CK's executed
在执行D CK时使用
actually and the test is not around then
实际上，测试还没到那时
so and we have the last job to go
所以，我们有最后的工作要做
quickly through which is the TC Karen
快速通过TC卡伦
job the DC Karen job just drops the DSD
DC Karen作业刚刚删除DSD
defy it grabs the ultra GlassFish with
违抗它抢夺与超GlassFish
the new API it grabs the TC k bundle see
抓取TC k包的新API，请参见
here it
在这里
grabs the TCK bundle it grabs at the SGD
在SGD处获取的TCK软件包
file it grabs the GlassFish and it again
文件，它抓住了GlassFish，然后再次
it puts armed to the exact location
它可以武装到确切的位置
where it is expected to be and the TSgt
预计会在哪里以及TSgt
files replaced in the TCK bundle to
在TCK捆绑包中替换的文件
basically this the ESET file does not
基本上，这个ESET文件不
need to be the same as the one used for
需要与用于
building to TCK and there is once this
建立到TCK，有一次
is done the TC Karen starts here so it's
完成了TC Karen从这里开始，所以
basically just these commands configure
基本上只是这些命令配置
I is set of an targets which configure
我设置了一个配置目标
the GlassFish it starts the GlassFish
GlassFish它启动GlassFish
and configure is GE users in in the
并在其中配置GE用户
glassfish some passwords probably or
glassfish可能有一些密码或
some other in whatever is needed for the
其他任何所需的
t ck to be done then there is called
要做，然后被称为
deploy which is target which deploys all
部署是部署所有目标的目标
the words in in the t ck bundle and
t ck捆绑包中的单词和
there is iran script which runs all the
有运行所有
tests so basically there is a few more
测试，所以基本上还有更多
few more parsing of the results so that
对结果进行更多的分析，以便
it can be used during the continuous
它可以在连续使用
build so if we will see that there are
建立，所以如果我们将看到有
some errors or failures then some email
一些错误或失败，然后一些电子邮件
can be sent saying well we some some
可以说我们有些
tests failed so someone needs to look at
测试失败，所以有人需要看看
it so it is probably mostly for some
所以大概是一些
future use if the t ck job is going to
如果t ck作业要用于
be used by the in
由中使用
for checking whether the changes in the
用于检查
implementation will be still comfortable
实施仍然会很舒适
with the begin with the API with
从API开始
specification so basically that's all
规范，所以基本上就是全部
it's all we just needed to be done I
这就是我们要做的所有事情
don't know any any questions what exact
不知道有什么问题
order did these need to run in and which
这些命令是否需要在其中运行？
ones will be created by the projects and
这些将由项目创建，
which one is going to be shared sounds
哪一个将被共享的声音
like yeah so the order and the order
像是的，所以秩序和秩序
yeah I I created this is mango which is
是的，我创造了这是芒果
like documentation in DJB see it doesn't
像DJB中的文档一样
actually matter whether you still build
不管你是否还在建造
the API and put it to GlassFish or
API并将其放入GlassFish或
however you build his GD file first once
但是你先建立他的GD文件
these steps are done then you can build
这些步骤完成后，您可以构建
the TCK with the DSGE file and then even
带有DSGE文件的TCK，然后甚至
the TCGA job is built and he can run the
TCGA的工作已经建立，他可以运行
TC case there is a northern exact order
TC案件有一个北方确切命令
which is needed to follow for it is TK
这是需要遵循的传统知识
to be done unless of course you need to
除非您当然需要
you need to build the TGA fast so GT
您需要快速构建TGA，以便GT
file creation the first build job is
文件创建的第一个构建工作是
second and round job is the last sorry
第二轮工作是最后的遗憾
what was the the other question which
另一个问题是什么
ones just does each project needed to
只是每个项目都需要
have all these jobs so it's each project
有所有这些工作，所以这是每个项目
gonna say for example build the TCK
比如说要建TCK
itself
本身
yes the CCA is not bill many way and it
是的，CCA并不是很多方法，它
is good for the project so that the
对项目有好处，因此
project can be dusted actually so it's
该项目实际上可以撒粉所以
not only for this particular use case
不仅针对此特定用例
this can be used in future project
可以在将来的项目中使用
development so whenever you if he if you
发展，所以只要你，如果他，如果你
have your own
有你自己的
TCK then you can actually test the
TCK，然后您可以实际测试
compatibility anytime chmm yeah and each
随时兼容chmm是的，每个
DC game is to build full four TCK to be
DC游戏是建立完整的四个TCK
an another option is we can we can we
另一个选择是我们可以
can probably grab all the CPS or Java EE
可以获取所有CPS或Java EE
is a saree jacket IEDC came like the
是IEDC的纱丽外套来了
whole bundle which is like 100 megabytes
整个捆绑，就像100兆字节
or whatever and the only tests from the
或其他任何唯一的测试
particular test folder can be run so um
可以运行特定的测试文件夹
that would mean that the project's can
这意味着该项目可以
use it see yes they don't need to build
用它看是的，他们不需要建立
a own TCK bundle but it is much
自己的TCK捆绑包，但很多
complicated because there is a class
复杂，因为有一堂课
path for all the CPS and properties for
所有CPS和属性的路径
all the particular technologies and
所有特定技术和
which probably the projects don't need
这些项目可能不需要
to know about it so um yeah you wouldn't
知道这一点，是的，你不会
you could use the whole CES bundle but
您可以使用整个CES捆绑包，但
at some cost
付出一些代价
okay the question is I thought at least
好吧，问题是我认为至少
what I thought that we should ask all
我认为我们应该问所有
our API stream in standalone TC Cranston
独立TC Cranston中的API流
20 ck test and we should use actually
20 ck测试，我们应该实际使用
the officially released bundle which is
正式发布的捆绑包是
available from there from eclipse
从eclipse那里可以得到
download it must be somewhere this
下载它一定在这个地方
scenario actually builds D CK's from
场景实际上是从
sources it deals from master right and
来源来自主权利，
what we have in TC k master maybe not
我们在TC k大师中所拥有的也许不是
exactly what we want because that
正是我们想要的，因为
officially released bundles maybe it can
正式发布的捆绑包也许可以
be somewhat in master some other things
掌握其他一些东西
added after that bundles Indonesia so do
之后将印度尼西亚捆绑在一起添加
we have maybe this is the question to
我们可能是这个问题
certification do we have a tag or leave
证明我们有标签还是离开
some kind of commit ID of that of then
当时的某种提交ID
these efficient final is created so we
创建了这些有效的决赛，所以我们
can get the sources compile them and
可以让源编译它们，并且
basically say that this is exactly what
基本上说这就是
is in that official bundle and we run
在那个官方包中，我们运行
tests based on that it is clear what I'm
根据测试，我很清楚
asking so we do a CD for j8 chemistry
问，所以我们为j8化学制作CD
sure that one is suitable and comin from
确保一个合适的人
CFG ask my question so the I'll just
CFG问我一个问题，这样我就
jump in
跳进去
while series getting ready to answer the
而系列准备回答
TC case and we will be using our push to
TC案例，我们将继续使用
the right now we're pushing them up to
现在我们要把他们推到
the Eclipse download here's some I'll
Eclipse下载，这里有一些
paste into the chat the the latest
将最新的内容粘贴到聊天中
Jack's BT cking I'm sorry that was Jason
杰克的BT结对不起，对不起，这就是杰森
being left my fault
被我责备
yes at but we gentle joint we need
是的，但是我们需要温和的联合
sources don't need a well either II
来源也不需要井II
ultimately so ultimately you have to
最终如此，最终您必须
build you have to run the test from the
建立您必须从运行测试
binary the pre-built TGK is right no
二进制预制的TGK是正确的否
that's actually what I have concerned
这实际上是我所关心的
about this job actually runs PC case
关于这项工作实际上是运行PC机箱
which are built from sources not from
从来源而不是来源构建
violence I saw that and the source on
我看到了暴力，而且来源
its own demise because Yan provides
自己的灭亡，因为阎提供
there the special that's jte or whatever
那里是特别的东西
it's called file which contains
它被称为文件，其中包含
classified information but the table
分类信息但表
right so question is do we have a source
对，所以问题是我们是否有资料来源
of that bundle you know with tag or
您知道的带有标签或
committee well yeah actually I think
委员会很好，是的，实际上我认为
you're mistaken
你误会了
um basically be the build bundle if it's
um基本上是构建包，如果它是
available I am NOT I was not aware about
有空我不是我不知道
than being available I think it would be
比有空我想
enough to use because this this contains
足以使用，因为这包含
this bundle contains all the sources it
该捆绑包包含了所有来源
contains all the binaries and the TIG t5
包含所有二进制文件和TIG t5
is maybe not properly configured but
可能配置不正确，但
that's whatever that's all you need to
那就是您所需要的一切
do to configure it cerium de Java EE TCK
进行配置cerium de Java EE TCK
the old Java EE D CK workflow was to
旧的Java EE D CK工作流程是
grab this bundle to configure D CK
获取此捆绑包以配置D CK
because you had to configure it because
因为您必须配置它，因为
you didn't know where the vendors
你不知道供应商在哪里
implementation would be would reside and
实施将驻留并
then around the D CK save a thing I
然后在D CK周围保存我的东西
think if we have this bundled and we
想想如果我们捆绑了这个，我们
don't need to build it we just need we
不需要建造它，我们只需要我们
just need to run it okay so it means
只需运行就可以了，这意味着
that having the bundle what ad just put
有捆绑广告的东西
a link to the chat it actually
实际聊天的链接
simplifies your job right yeah yeah it's
是的，可以简化您的工作，是的
uh replaces one one of this job I I have
嗯取代了我有一份工作
I wouldn't need to build it on my own
我不需要自己构建
okay okay in this case maybe the next
好的，在这种情况下，也许下一个
action item for you would be actually
您的行动项目实际上是
modify your drop today that it actually
今天修改您的下落，实际上
uses their bundle instead of building
使用他们的捆绑包而不是建筑
TCK itself which is what we've what the
TCK本身就是我们所拥有的
quantity is
数量是
okay okay that's all this comment that
好吧，好吧，这就是所有评论
you know the goal is that we're
你知道目标是我们
verifying the TCK that's going to be
验证将要使用的TCK
shipped to the world is valid right so
运到世界上是正确的，所以
at some point there's gonna be you know
在某个时候，你会知道
a door somebody proposing some binaries
有人提出一些二进制文件的门
and saying we expect that these are
并说我们期望这些是
perfect
完善
this TCK build is perfect and we're
这个TCK版本非常完美，我们
gonna ship it to the world we need
将其运送到我们需要的世界
somebody to run it and verify that it is
有人来运行它并确认它是
perfect and they can't ignore the binary
完美，他们不能忽略二进制
and go build another binary they need to
并建立他们需要的另一个二进制文件
use that binary because that's the one
使用那个二进制文件，因为那是一个
that other implementations are going to
其他实现将
use to certify so that's the goal so we
用于认证，所以这就是目标，所以我们
so we do run certain qualification tests
所以我们会进行某些资格测试
on teeth on those tcks before they're
在他们之前的牙齿上
pushed so I guess the question may be
推，所以我想问题可能是
the question you're asking is what is
您要问的问题是什么
that
那
or the pre-staging test sufficient you
或预测试足以
know that's certainly a good question we
知道这肯定是一个好问题，我们
could go through that well they are when
可以顺利通过他们当时
they're built they get run they're
他们建立了，他们得到运行，他们是
tested against the Eclipse class just
仅针对Eclipse类进行了测试
five about one project for the building
五个关于一个建筑项目
excuse me that makes sense yeah it makes
对不起，这是有道理的
sense yep so but it sounds like we are
是的，是的，但听起来像我们
able to pull this binary down and run it
能够拉下这个二进制文件并运行它
like like anybody would that it just
就像任何人都会那样
like Yun said the zip file contains the
像Yun所说的zip文件包含
binary the pre built it also contains
预构建的二进制文件还包含
all the sources the thing that I guess
所有来源我猜的东西
that we would apply the signature to is
我们将签名应用于的是
the zip bundle itself so that as long as
拉链包本身，只要
D and as long as the compatible
D和只要兼容
implementation is able to represent that
实现能够代表
they're running the test using a de
他们正在使用de运行测试
bundle I think that it seems like that
捆绑我觉得好像
should be enough that isn't to say
应该足够，不用说
they're using the right
他们正在使用正确的
that's perfect I think it was kinda
太好了，我认为这有点
slightly different topic right because
主题略有不同，因为
what we are discussing now that's
我们现在正在讨论的是
testing api's for compatibility this DC
测试api是否兼容此DC
case for correctness is I guess it's out
正确性的理由是我猜出来了
of scope of this demonstration right
此示范权的范围
exactly yeah so difficult I was
是的，我真的很难
understanding it was the same call I'm
知道那是我的同一个电话
okay alone it's just a different it's a
好吧，只是不同而已
different team of people that would be
不同的人会
on the PC from the teeth decay group
在PC上，来自蛀牙组
okay okay so when this runs I noticed
好的，好的，所以当它运行时，我注意到
that it was setting the port to 8080
将端口设置为8080
right and if you have 30 jobs on this
对，如果您有30个工作
thing all running at the same time using
事情都在同时运行
the same port you're gonna get conflicts
您将在同一端口上发生冲突
on the test run and it's correct 40th
在测试运行中，它是正确的40
some dck is designed to run one test at
一些dck旨在在以下位置运行一项测试
a time so yeah when when one test
是的，是的，当一个测试的时候
finishes and in you can own the other
完成，你可以拥有另一个
test so how are we gonna handle that
测试，我们该如何处理
because if we have individual projects
因为如果我们有单独的项目
set up this and they are expecting to
设置这个，他们期望
start a glassfish on port 8080 that we
在8080端口启动一个玻璃鱼
you know we can't let them run at the
你知道我们不能让他们在
same time yes this is this is handled by
同时是的，这是由
the Jenkins on the Eclipse IDE each job
Jenkins在Eclipse IDE上的每项工作
is executed in a virtual environment
在虚拟环境中执行
where you you are virtually alone so you
在哪里，你几乎是一个人，所以你
just can start
可以开始
whatever whatever number of jobs and he
不管有多少工作，他
all started lost fishing in on 8080 and
所有人都在8080年开始钓鱼了，
and it works just fine I was using like
它工作得很好，我正在使用像
a docker container um well I'm not
一个码头集装箱，嗯，我不是
expert but I was told that they are
专家，但我被告知他们是
using some enterprising in so on using
使用一些进取的
using some yeah I don't remember the
是的，我不记得了
name yeah yeah basically dance then it
名字是的，基本上是跳舞，然后
looks similar to dr. yeah okay all right
看起来和博士相似是的，好吧
saying its own sandbox so we should not
说自己的沙箱，所以我们不应该
worry about that for clean right yes so
为清洁而担心
if we don't have if we use that zip file
如果没有，则使用该zip文件
that's posted to the Downloads directory
已发布到下载目录
which of these steps would still be
这些步骤中的哪一个仍然是
necessary
必要
ah you definitely need to have the TSgt
啊，你一定要有TSgt
file yeah that's the primary
是的，这是主要的
configuration file so it's TTS jte then
配置文件，所以是TTS jte
we need to JSON be API for example then
例如，我们需要将JSON作为API
the pre-built
预建
API integration yes you need lots of you
API集成是的，您需要很多人
need to have the glass fascia again
需要再次有玻璃筋膜
which you will around the TC k so yeah
你会在TC k周围这样吗
you probably need have any you need the
您可能需要任何您需要的
job which builds the API you need the
构建您需要的API的工作
job which may receive GlassFish you need
可能会收到您需要的GlassFish的工作
to the job which sha stubs the SGD file
应将SGD文件存根的工作
and you need the job which arounds bck
而你需要围绕bck的工作
so you need for jobs is it those four
所以你需要工作是那四个
that you have on the page just because
您在页面上拥有的仅仅是因为
because you didn't use the exact words
因为你没有使用确切的词
that are written and I don't know what
写的，我不知道是什么
they do precisely that's what was kind
他们确实就是那样
of the question so is those four right
问题是那四个是正确的
no actually no this one is oh you know
不，实际上不，这个是哦，你知道
what yeah you are right
是的，你是对的
uh yeah useful okay so every project
嗯是有用的，所以每个项目
needs those 400 or something like those
需要那些400或类似的东西
four right so basically it's for every
四个正确的，所以基本上每个
you have a directory with all the kind
您拥有所有目录
of flavors of the tsjt e for the
tsjt e的口味
different specs that have standalone
具有独立规格的不同规格
tcks for example ejv does not have a
tcks例如ejv没有
standalone TCGA where is that directory
独立的TCGA，该目录在哪里
can you point me at that again that
你能再指出我一次吗
wasn't a CTS directory yes - basically
不是CTS目录，是的-基本上
it's in D CK folder install the
它在D CK文件夹中安装
technology and bin there's sgt file so
技术和bin有sgt文件，所以
under install there's how many yes under
在安装下有多少个是
install there's Tugg file for each
安装每个的Tugg文件
technology for launching so that's how
发射技术，就是这样
many Jenkins job that's how many sets of
詹金斯的工作是多少套
Jenkins job yeah this number times four
詹金斯（Jenkins）工作，是这个数字的四倍
right yes so I'll just interject that
是的，所以我将其插入
there are a few standalone TZ case that
有一些独立的TZ盒
are not listed here so if they add those
没有在这里列出，所以如果他们添加那些
if you're trying to come up with a total
如果您想得出一个总数
number yep
是的
that's the goal what which ones are not
这是目标，哪些不是
listed well yeah
列出的很好
anything that doesn't have a standalone
任何没有独立的东西
test so EJB I think there's a few others
测试EJB，我认为还有其他一些
I'm sorry I don't have that list on my
对不起，我没有这份清单
off the top of my head there's also tcks
从我头顶上也有斑点
like for CDI for java male that are not
像CDI的Java男性一样
extracted from this collection yes how
从这个集合中提取是
he has to be in validation as well about
他还必须进行验证
the IBM about that and the other one
IBM关于这一点，另一个
from Bob Lee it has inject do we have
从Bob Lee那里注入了我们有
that TCK by the way do we need to have
那个TCK，我们需要
that in some way well that's not
在某种程度上，那不是
project thunder us at the moment yeah
此刻打雷我们，是的
but II wouldn't need is for the complete
但是我不需要的是完整的
implementation but that's not the that's
实施，但这不是
not necessary
不必要
run so we don't we're not releasing that
运行，所以我们不释放它
API jar and we're not releasing that TCK
API jar，我们不会发布该TCK
or we don't have any spec work to be
或我们没有任何规范工作
done yes
是的
[Music]
[音乐]
nothing from a specification project
规范项目中没有
perspective to do so in in the just
公正地做到这一点
gonna say in the TCK jobs and he scaped
要在TCK工作中说，他逃了出来
we do have a there is a job there that
我们确实有一份工作，
runs that it runs all of those they're
运行它运行所有他们
just one as externally developed PC case
只是一个外部开发的PC机箱
okay so so if we produce an artifact so
好吧，所以如果我们产生一个假象，
if CDI for example is going to produce
例如CDI是否要生产
an artifact that is under Jakarta then
当时在雅加达之下的文物
it should be tested and they would test
应该测试一下，他们会测试
it presumably they'll test it will be
大概他们会测试
tested against um you know whatever
经过测试，你知道
criteria were used originally um or it
标准最初是用um还是
can be tested against a glass dish build
可以针对玻璃盘构建进行测试
because I believe somewhere in the chest
因为我相信在胸部的某个地方
jobs we have a CDI I think it's called
我有一个叫做CDI的工作
Stevie reminds me it's um I can't
Stevie提醒我，我不能
remember the name sorry anyway the
无论如何记得对不起这个名字
soldier is clearly us there is a cgi job
士兵显然是我们有一份cgi工作
there media agile let me let me add to
那里有媒体敏捷性，让我让我添加到
that at Alinea so there are actually 22
在Alinea，所以实际上有22
tcks that we build from this Jakarta ATC
我们从这个雅加达ATC建立的tcks
careful I apart from that we have scary
小心我除了我们有恐怖
I BB and be a porting PC case along with
我是BB，是随身携带PC机箱
that we have Java male JSF and debugging
我们有Java男性JSF和调试
support ec case which are lying outside
支撑在外面的电子琴盒
this particular repo but we are building
这个特殊的回购，但我们正在建立
it and generating the TC k button
它并生成TC k按钮
powering the eclipse from the location
从位置为日食供电
okay said that sounds helpful in did it
好的，这听起来很有帮助
so in situations where there is no
所以在没有
stand-alone TZ case such as
独立的TZ机壳，例如
EJB you know how are you past everyone
EJB，您知道每个人过得如何
but those those tests get run by
但是那些测试通过
selecting than whatever the prerequisite
选择比任何先决条件
subsets of CVS or write over it or so
CVS的子集或将其覆盖
you when you so when you look at the CTS
您，当您如此看CTS时
test Runner you'll see a whole bunch of
测试Runner，您会看到一大堆
the EJB related subset tests for example
例如，与EJB相关的子集测试
yeah yeah just wondering via the ant
是的，只是想知道通过蚂蚁
setup how are you I forget cuz it's been
设置你好吗我忘记了因为
a while so one a week and we documented
大约一个星期，我们记录了一下
clearly what tests we would expect you
显然我们期望您进行哪些测试
know the signature tests have a pretty
知道签名测试有一个漂亮的
specific name and I forget exactly
具体的名字，我忘了
because it's been a while that since
因为已经有一段时间了
I've learned them to see care myself
我学会了他们自己看护
what that looks like so what we would
看起来像什么，我们会怎样
have to set up in the job we have an
必须在工作中建立我们有一个
example job of a TCK that doesn't have a
TCK没有工作的示例工作
standalone we would have an example job
独立的，我们将有一个示例工作
of a run we need to do for a TCK that
我们需要为TCK做的
isn't standalone so I asked a couple
不是独立的，所以我问了几个
questions is he documented exactly what
问题是他确切记录了什么
it's necessary to run to certify egb I
有必要运行认证egb我
don't know I haven't looked we generally
不知道我没看过
just run the full up when we're
当我们
releasing or when we're qualifying on
发布或当我们有资格
GlassFish building we just run the whole
GlassFish大楼，我们只负责整个运营
thing and wait you know and we work on
事情，等你知道，我们正在努力
it until we pass all the tests right and
直到我们通过所有测试，然后
I'm if easy to run I would have to defer
我很容易跑，我不得不推迟
to either in the EJB team or to the TC
到EJB团队或TC
cave folks to if we wanted to come to
如果我们想来找人
suggest a subset of the CTS tests to run
建议要运行的CTS测试的子集
I'm sorry that's clear enough up but but
对不起，我已经很清楚了，但是
I was just curious
我只是好奇而已
so I forget are the signature tests
所以我忘记了签名测试
under for EJB under the EJB set of
在EJB集下的EJB下
packages or the signature test at a top
包装或签名测试在顶部
level
水平
separately yeah they are under the unity
是的，他们是在统一之下
folder
夹
you keep your Jess yes yes rej be okay
你保持你的杰西是的是瑞吉没事
yeah
是的
the signature tester under each the
每个签名下的签名测试器
technology all right do we have
技术好吗我们有
I think this if you made my screen this
我想如果你把我的屏幕做成这个
okay I'm sorry I think I made a mistake
好吧，对不起，我想我做错了
yeah yeah yeah so we need to run two
是的，所以我们需要运行两个
sets of tests we need to run basically
我们需要基本运行的测试集
comms on TS tests DJ no signature chest
TS测试DJ的通讯没有签名箱
EJB foregin yeah
EJB foregin是的
when we run either be tested we run all
当我们进行测试时，我们将全部运行
the tests under the HIV folder and he's
HIV文件夹下的测试，他是
in addition to that beat select the test
除了节拍，选择测试
under signature touch folder and EJB so
在签名触摸文件夹和EJB下
that's how we run all the tests and so
这就是我们运行所有测试的方式，因此
go ahead I was good as just if I could
继续吧，我很好，就好像我可以
share I can show you the subset tests
分享我可以向您展示子集测试
that are in them the piece of kidding
在他们那里开玩笑
sure okay thank you
当然可以，谢谢
yep okay so this is can you see my
是的，好的，这是你能看到我的吗
screen
屏幕
yes
是
I guess off the top of my head I would
我想我会从头顶上掉下来
say we would document at all for example
说我们将全部记录下来
EJB all of this all of these tests you
EJB所有这些测试
start with you jbd and run right and
从您开始jbd并正确运行，然后
then and we have this is a student this
然后，我们有这个学生
is actually a fully parameterised test
实际上是一个完全参数化的测试
runner you build your test
跑步者，您进行测试
implementation of GlassFish you can
可以执行GlassFish
leave it in if you build it in in the
如果您将其构建在
Jenkins system you can just point this
詹金斯系统你可以指出这一点
to the Jenkins wherever that let that
到詹金斯去的那个地方
artifact was created and then you run
工件已创建，然后运行
these tests and select you can select
这些测试并选择您可以选择
the set of subsets tests you want to run
您要运行的子集测试集
by default it would pick them all
默认情况下，它将全部选中
so you click all these and then you just
所以你点击所有这些，然后你就
say building parameters
说建筑参数
the only things that are required the
唯一需要的是
only thing as required is a you know
唯一需要的是你知道
your full GlassFish bundle
您完整的GlassFish捆绑包
yeah my friend yeah yeah I just went on
是的，我的朋友，是的，我只是继续
how this relates to the to the jobs that
这与工作有何关系
Yan showed so this is these are not
颜秀秀所以这不是
customized what Yan showed our
定制了Yan展示我们的内容
customized builds that will continue to
定制的构建将继续
move forward and involved with the
前进并参与
project these these tests just pull from
投影这些测试只是从
the the established promoted the
建立的提升
promoted PCK jars or zip file excuse me
升级的PCK罐子或zip文件对不起
and then they run the tests in a very
然后他们在非常
prescribed set up I
规定的设置我
don't have a I have no objection to
没有我不反对
these what I'm sorry what I'm looking at
这些对不起我在看什么
right now is the CTS test suite runner
现在是CTS测试套件亚军
and I there I don't think there's any
我在那里我不认为有任何
reason projects can't use that
原因项目不能使用它
we also have a similar job to this one
我们也有与此类似的工作
that can run that can run the standalone
可以运行，可以独立运行
tcks
cks
but again it requires a glassfish build
但这又需要一条玻璃鱼
sir you know the problem here in eclipse
先生，您知道日食的问题
permissions I suppose that to run a joke
权限我想开个玩笑
on some to make it a part of your
在某些方面使其成为您的一部分
pipeline initiated from some project
从某个项目启动的管道
that user who runs it needs to have
运行它的用户需要
access yes
访问是
TCK right and yes are not committed
TCK正确，是，不承诺
certificate right correct that's correct
证书权利正确是正确的
so you could one could clone this what
所以你可以克隆这个
we were trying to avoid was having to
我们试图避免不得不
clone this hold this job these this job
复制此职位担任此职位这些职位
or the TCK test runners all right so
或TCK测试选手都可以
they I think John and the the ds1 B team
他们我认为John和ds1 B团队
they started I think they started for
他们开始了，我想他们开始了
this but I shouldn't speak for them and
这个，但我不应该为他们说话，
then they just customize it and got rid
然后他们只是自定义它并摆脱了
of all the things to help me
所有可以帮助我的事情
personally I I think for long long-term
我个人认为长期长期
results having a customized job is the
具有定制工作的结果是
way is is definitely the way to go if we
如果我们去的话，这绝对是必经之路
get to a point where we just need some
达到我们只需要一些的地方
projects to to finalize their test
完成测试的项目
results or if a project just says I I
结果或项目是否只说II
had there's no you know I don't need to
如果没有，你知道我不需要
run to create a customized job I'm sure
可以运行以创建自定义作业
we can arrange to have you know either
我们可以安排让您知道
to just copy and paste clone the jobs
只需复制并粘贴克隆作业
here into that that that sub project but
在那个子项目中，但是
or we could arrange to have those tests
否则我们可以安排进行这些测试
run and then we can archive the results
运行，然后我们可以将结果存档
so each time it runs the test it shaves
所以每次运行测试都会刮胡子
off all of the test results and these
所有的测试结果和这些
can be archived SDM you know as for
可以将SDM存档
submission you know to a suspect to the
将您认识的犯罪嫌疑人提交给
specification committee for example
例如规格委员会
mm-hmm okay are there are there other
嗯嗯还有其他吗
questions
问题
okay it means it means I am top in
好的，这意味着我名列前茅
reporting
报告
you
您